NITZAN COHEN

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Rishon LeZiyyon +972-50-3131570 (074-7271127) nitzancohen@hotmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/nitzancohen-web https://github.com/NitzanCO7

PROFILE SUMMARY

As a web developer with over 10 years of experience in the education field, I have a unique perspective on the power of technology in enhancing the learning process. Specializing in implementing cutting-edge technological tools, I have been able to make a positive impact on the lives of students with diverse learning needs.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Java Script HTML CSS React Redux Node.js Express.js MongoDB Git & GitHub Vercel

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Freelancer

Aug, 2022 - present

- Developed and powered a dynamic, responsive, and user-friendly single-page application (SPA) for a small businesses using React.js (shayelbornshtein.com, Running Trainer)
- · Built a chat application for non-verbal individuals using ReactJS and deployed it with Vercel to a custom domain (we-talk.fun)

Special Education Teacher Ministry of Education

2016 - present

- · Implemented the use of advanced technology across my team, such as assistive devices and adaptive software, to enhance learning experiences and promote student independence.
- · Specialized in providing individualized instruction and support to students with diverse learning needs and disabilities.
- · Implemented evidence-based teaching strategies and accommodations to meet the unique needs of each student and improve their academic and social outcomes.
- · Collaborated with interdisciplinary teams, including speech therapists, occupational. therapists, and parents, to develop and implement individualized education plans (IEPs)

Long-Distances Running Coach Eitan - Everybody can

2019 - present

Training people with autism in athletics fields to improve their motor skills and also their communication skills.

Mentor National Service 2007 - 2010

Volunteer at Association for children with Cerebral Palsy (CP) in Rishon LeZiyyon.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development | Practicum by Yandex & MasterSchool

2021 - 2022

- Completed an intensive program focused on developing full-stack development skills.
- Acquired hands-on experience with a range of technologies and tools, gaining a strong foundation in full-stack web development.

Long-Distances Running Coach Certificate

School of Sport Professions

2019

Teacher Certificate in Special Education Ohalo Academic College

2016 - 2017

BA Special Education Tel-Hai Academic College

2011 - 2016

Practical Electronics Engineering

Mekif Gimel "Amit Amal"

2005 - 2007

LANGUAGES

Hebrew Native

English

Full working proficiency